	var trivia_questions = [{question: 'How many reincarnations have there been of the Dalai Lama?',
				answer: 13},
				{
				question: 'How many gallons of milk does a cow produce per week?',
				answer: 25,
				},
				{
				question: 'How fast can a horse run (mph)?',
				answer: 30,
				},
				{
				question: 'How many countries are there in the world?',
				answer: 196,
				},
				{
					question: 'What percent of food and drink sold in the US is organic?',
					answer: 4,
				},
				{
					question: 'What percent of the population is left handed?',
					answer: 13,
				},
				{
					question: 'How many dollars does the average American spend at vending machines during a year?',
					answer: 27,
				},
				{
					question: 'How many hours does an average cat sleep in a day?',
					answer: 16,
				},{
					question: 'What percent of Americans say that they are often stressed at work?',
					answer: 30,
				},{
					question: 'How many years does it take a plastic bag to degrade?',
					answer: 1000,
				},{
					question: 'What percent of total electricity consumption goes to refrigerators?',
					answer: 7,
				},{
					question: 'What is the estimated age of the universe in billions of years?',
					answer: 13.75,
				},{
					question: "What percent of the body's nutrients is consumed by the brain?",
					answer: 25,
				},{
					question: 'How many bones are there in the human body?',
					answer: 206,
				},
				{question: 'What is the height of Mt. Everest in kilometers?',
				answer: 8.8},
				];

// give positive or negative feedback depending on whether they were in the interval
var trivia_positives = ['The correct answer was within your confidence interval!',
'The answer was in your confidence interval again!',
];
var trivia_negatives = ['The answer was not in your confidence interval. Perhaps 90% confidence intervals should be wider than you think.',
"The answer was again not in your confidence interval."];


